Made Fresh Since 1960

For Franchising Info, Call [480.688.8914](tel:480.688.8914)

MenuNavigateResearch TacoTime – What Is TacoTime®? – The TacoTime Brand Story – Why Fast-Casual Mexican Food is Hot? – What Are My Startup Costs? – How Much Can I Make? – What’s Special About Our Menu? – What Are The Available Markets? – TacoTime Franchisee Reviews – Why Do Our Customers Love Us? – TacoTime FAQ – Top 10 Reasons to Own a TacoTime Franchise – Next Steps Startup Costs Request Franchise Info News & Blog

Privacy Policy
==============

TacoTime Franchise understands the importance of protecting the privacy of its website users. The information collected is used to market and improve the services we offer, to improve the web site content, and to contact you with updates to the web site or for other marketing purposes.

Certain areas of this site, require registration or a password for access. Information obtained from registered users of these areas may also be used for TacoTime Franchise marketing purposes, and cookies may be used in those and other areas, as is described in this Policy. Information obtained in these areas may also be used in accordance with agreements governing access to and use of the specific areas. In addition, visitors of this website may choose to register for a Login user ID and password to simplify access to some interactive features on this website. Log file data and other information gathered from registered users of this website are used to improve the customer experience while on our website.

**What information does TacoTime Franchise capture about visitors to its web** **site?**

Our web server uses an extended log file format, which captures: date and time of visit, referring address (location from which a visitor comes to this website), type of Internet browser, and visitor’s IP address. (Each computer that connects to the Internet is assigned a unique number, an IP address, for identification purposes). The log file does not capture a visitor’s email address.

**Does TacoTime Franchise ask for personal information?**

Several areas of this website may ask for personal information. In these areas, your name, address, email address, billing information, and business profile are requested. This information is collected to help us further develop our services, to provide you access to valuable TacoTime Franchise Internet-based information and services, and to bill you for those services if you elect to use them.

**Does TacoTime Franchise share my information?**

We may disclose personally identifying information (PII) about you:

*       **With our service providers:** We contract with companies who help with parts of our business operations. We require that our service providers only use your PII in connection with the services they perform for us.
*       **With service providers to our Advertisers:** Our Advertisers may contract with companies who handle data (such as Advertisers’ customer lists) for them.
*       **With our subsidiaries and related companies**
*       **In connection with legal proceedings:** When we are under a legal obligation to do so, for example to comply with a binding order of a court, or where disclosure is necessary to exercise, establish or defend the legal rights of TacoTime, our Advertisers or any other third party.
*       **In connection with a sale of our business:** If a third party acquires some or all of our business or assets, we may disclose your PII in connection with the sale.

We also share technical data that we collect about your browsing habits and your device (such as data relating to our cookies, tracking pixels and similar technologies) with other advertising companies in the digital advertising ecosystem. This enables them and us to better target ads to you.

Finally, we may disclose aggregated, anonymized information to our Advertisers and other third parties.

**How does TacoTime Franchise use the information?**

The information collected through this site helps us identify the type of web site content our customers value most. We use this information to market and improve the web site and our services. We also use this information to send you email notifications about updates to the web site, and to contact you by other means for marketing and other purposes. Our policy is to not give, sell or otherwise distribute the information collected through this site to third parties outside of TacoTime Franchise (unless required by law); provided, however, in some cases we may use suppliers to assist us in collecting, using or otherwise processing for our benefit the information obtained through this site. Our practice is to require our suppliers to conduct such activities consistent with this policy and our requirements.

**What is a cookie?**

A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a web site, is placed by the web server into the browser’s application folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the web site to “recognize” you as a unique individual.

**Does TacoTime Franchise use cookies?**

Cookies are used to achieve two goals. The first is to provide TacoTime Franchise with the capability to personalize information for certain segments of its customer base. Secondly, in some instances, cookies are used to allow TacoTime Franchise the opportunity to associate individual customers with their information profiles. For example, through the use of cookies, the website can “remember” your user ID when you login to TacoTime Franchise at this website on your computer.

**Can cookies be removed from my hard drive?**

Yes, cookies can be removed from your hard drive. Also, depending on what type of web browser and what browser version you are using, you may be able to change the properties on your cookie file so that cookies are not used or saved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on removing cookies.

**Can I opt out from receiving further communication?**

We recognize how important your online privacy is to you, so we offer the following options for controlling the targeted ads you receive and how we use your data:

*       **You can opt-out of receiving targeted ads served by us:** You can opt out of receiving targeted ads served by us or on our behalf by clicking on the blue icon in the corner of the ads we serve. Please note that, if you delete your cookies or upgrade your browser after having opted out, you will need to opt out again. Furthermore, if you use multiple browsers or devices, you will need to execute this opt out on each browser or device.
*       **You can opt-out of receiving targeted ads from us or other companies:** You may use the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) opt out tool, which will allow you to opt out of seeing targeted ads from us and from NAI approved member companies.

You may opt out of receiving targeted ads from other companies that perform ad targeting services by visiting the DAA [website,](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) and Your Online Choices [website](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

TacoTime Franchise reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy at any time, with or without notice. Please check back frequently in the event of changes. Your use of this website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy.

Research Franchise

Sitemap

For Franchise Info, Call
------------------------

### [480.688.8914](tel:480.688.8914)

For Consumer Info, Call
-----------------------

### [480.688.8914](tel:480.688.8914)

© 2024 Kahala Franchising, L.L.C. All rights reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://www.tacotime.com/about/privacy/index.php) | [480.688.8914](tel:480.688.8914)

You may submit additional information and questions to TacoTime Franchise Development Department at:  
Franchising@kahalamgmt.com or Kahala Franchising, LLC – 9311 E. Via de Ventura, Scottsdale, AZ 85258

All trademarks referenced are property of their respective owners. The information provided herein is for informational purposes only and is not intended as an offer to sell, or the solicitation of an offer to buy, a franchise; nor is it directed to the residents of any particular jurisdiction within the U.S. or elsewhere. The following states currently regulate the offer and sale of franchises: CA, HI, IL, IN, MD, MI, MN, NY, ND, RI, SD, VA, WA, and WI. If you are a resident of one of these states, or of a jurisdiction that has similar requirements, we will not offer you a franchise until we have completed the applicable registration (or obtained the exemption from registration) and complied with any other applicable pre-sale registration and/or disclosure requirements in the applicable jurisdiction. Regardless of what state you reside in, an offering can only be made by a franchise disclosure document.
